<sdsdialog name="AE Distribution" width="100" height="200" layout="tabbedpane">
   <description>
   	This process compares distributions of adverse events and demographic variables across treatment arms.
   </description>

	<sdstabbedpane name="General">

		<include href="CDISCFolders.xml" />

      <include href="AETermLevel.xml" />
      
      <include href="AEGroupLevel.xml" />
      
		<include href="NTrtUse.xml" />

		<include href="TreatVars.xml" />

		<include href="AESerTEOnly.xml" />

		<input name="CountMultiple" type="checkbox" label="Count multiple occurrences of an event per subject" required="false" value="No">
			<description>
				Select the method by which to compute counts of adverse events.  If you select Subject Occurrence, counts will
				reflect the number of subjects that experienced an adverse event.  Each subject will only contribute one time
				to the occurrence count of an event, regardless of how many times that specific event may have occurred to the subject. Note, for selecting the
				representative event occurrence per subject, the data is sorted to take the first event occurring to a subject based on seriousness (AESER), severity
				(AESEV or AETOXGR), and Study day (AESTDY).  If you select
				Total Occurrence, the distribution display will represent overall counts of events, including multipler occurrences per subjects.
			</description>
		</input>
		
		<input name="PropThresh" type="slider" label="Percent Occurrence Threshold" value="0">
			<range domain="real" min="0" max="15" ndec="2" />
			<description>
					Enter a threshold for which to display adverse events  
					Only events that occur above the entered threshold (in terms of overall percent of subject 
					occurrence) will be displayed initially.  The threshold can be dynamically changed on the resulting 
					output dashboard.
			</description>
		</input>				

	</sdstabbedpane>

	<sdstabbedpane name="Filters">
		
		<include href="SubjectFilter.xml" />

		<input name="AEDeltaDrop" type="list1" label="Include the following adverse events:"
		  options="All,New" value="All">
		  <description>
				Choose which records to include in the analysis.  Most relevant when trying to subset to records that are new when study data has been updated and compared
				to previous snapshot.  New shows records newly available in recent snapshot. All includes  all available records (subject to other record filtering, e.g. with the where statement). 
		  </description>
		</input>

		<include href="AEWhereStmt.xml" />

		<include href="Populations.xml" />
		
		<include href="ClinicalByVars.xml" />

	</sdstabbedpane>

	<sdstabbedpane name="Output">
	
		<input name="Distribution_OutData" label="Output Data Set" type="textfield" maxlength="32">
			<description>
				Name the output SAS data set to be created by this process.
				If you leave this blank, the default name StudyName_aed will be used.
			</description>
		</input>

		<input name="DistributionScript" label="JMP Script Output File Name" type="outfile" value="" extension="jsl" autolaunch="Y" hidden="SDS" required="SDS">
			<description>
				Name the output JMP script file (.jsl)
				containing script to display results.
			</description>
		</input>

		<include href="OutPath.xml" />

	</sdstabbedpane>

</sdsdialog>
